Finding Aid for Phi Beta Kappa. Alpha Chapter (University of Michigan) records, 1907-1978
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Phi Beta Kappa. Alpha Chapter (University of Michigan) records 1907-1978
Phi Beta Kappa. Alpha Chapter (University of Michigan)
1 linear foot and 1 oversize folder
87369 Bimu F41 2
ABSTRACT
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
A portion of the records was transferred from the Graduate Library of the University of Michigan (donor no. 1278 ) and from the Alpha Chapter (donor no. 6214 ).
The record group is open to research.
The Alpha Chapter of Phi Beta Kappa was established at the University of Michigan in 1907. The chapter was an outgrowth of a society which had started in the spring of 1907, known as the Alpha Honor Society. The organization was established to recognize intellectual and scholarly achievements of students.
The record group includes minutes of meetings, financial records, and correspondence and miscellaneous other papers.
Subjects:
University of Michigan--Honorary societies.
- Alpha Chapter records
  - Charter, 1907 (Folder Bimu F41)
    (in oversize folder Bimu F41 Out)
  - Correspondence, 1907-1908 (Box 1)
  - Papers, 1907-1917 and undated (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1907-1930 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1907-1930, typescript (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1930-1952 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1952-1966 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1966-1978 (Box 1)
  - Minutes of the Executive Board, 1930-1937, typescript (Box 1)
  - Financial records, 1928-1959 (Box 1)
  - Financial records, 1960-1968 (Box 1)